[{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88acc"},"rt":31813,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":88605,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88acd"},"rt":28321,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117014,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ace"},"rt":12521,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129680,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88acf"},"rt":44259,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":174023,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad0"},"rt":65844,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239997,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad2"},"rt":7817,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":253222,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad3"},"rt":14014,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267322,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad4"},"rt":38445,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305856,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad5"},"rt":18369,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":324311,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad6"},"rt":27746,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352158,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad7"},"rt":10083,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":362333,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad8"},"rt":14039,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":376456,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ad9"},"rt":23105,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":399651,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88ada"},"rt":10581,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410316,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88adb"},"rt":48532,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459136,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88aec"},"rt":99599,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":167788,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88aed"},"rt":41643,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":209741,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"12D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88aee"},"rt":85885,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":295727,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"3C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88aef"},"rt":45636,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":341913,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PM04 PMH 08 AM01 PMU U K K K K J J H H H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af0"},"rt":84820,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":426839,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af2"},"rt":13450,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":452361,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PME G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af3"},"rt":45989,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":498448,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af4"},"rt":31955,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":530508,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af5"},"rt":84555,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":615160,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af6"},"rt":17948,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":633398,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af7"},"rt":14081,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":647607,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M C L L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af8"},"rt":43412,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":691117,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88af9"},"rt":48712,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":739928,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88afa"},"rt":21481,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":761507,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88afb"},"rt":95969,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":857579,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"02 PMC C C C C O 02 PM02 PMX O 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b0c"},"rt":15434,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":50575,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM11 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b0d"},"rt":25039,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75717,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b0e"},"rt":10084,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85910,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b0f"},"rt":12434,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":98454,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b10"},"rt":6294,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104855,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b12"},"rt":18141,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":126084,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b13"},"rt":7558,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134015,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":"05 PM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b14"},"rt":34144,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":168265,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":6,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,E,I,J,K,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b15"},"rt":20811,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":189181,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G,M","hovered":"J X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b16"},"rt":5304,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194594,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b17"},"rt":14991,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209695,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b18"},"rt":4462,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214262,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b19"},"rt":47968,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":262336,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N,X","hovered":"02 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b1a"},"rt":11527,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273969,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P","hovered":"01 PM02 PM10 AM05 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b1b"},"rt":11045,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285118,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b2c"},"rt":48017,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154863,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"12 PM11 AMZ Z F F 10 AM09 AM10 AMC 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b2d"},"rt":33806,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":188848,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"1K D D K 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b2e"},"rt":36195,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":225146,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMC 09 AM09 AMC 11 AM11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b2f"},"rt":11687,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":236926,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"B B H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b30"},"rt":116931,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":353958,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I 08 AMO I U U 03 PM02 PMO 02 PMF O 09 AMC 09 AMC C C 10 AMA A F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b32"},"rt":16257,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":377564,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"45E E 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b33"},"rt":70822,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448525,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F G B B B B B B B C F B M M M M 12 PMM X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b34"},"rt":68545,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":517554,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B X X X 03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMF B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b35"},"rt":33059,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":550997,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J E 09 AMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b36"},"rt":11908,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":563003,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b37"},"rt":9163,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572267,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM01 PM12 PMM M 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b38"},"rt":8868,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":581231,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b39"},"rt":36798,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":618123,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"09 AMZ Z N N 06 PM04 PMZ Z Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b3a"},"rt":12127,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":630430,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"09 AM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b3b"},"rt":65663,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":696191,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PM02 PMX K K 09 AMJ 07 PM07 PM06 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b4c"},"rt":8915,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58701,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"04 PMJ 03 PM11 AMC C 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b4d"},"rt":7601,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66360,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM10 AMU D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b4e"},"rt":18494,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84910,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"10 AM12 PM01 PMZ C C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b4f"},"rt":49818,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":134774,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,U","hovered":"01 PMZ A Z Z F O O O A 04 PM03 PMU U 12 PM12 PMZ Z F F O 11 AMZ Z I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b50"},"rt":64651,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199517,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PMI I I Z I I I I O 11 AM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMU 12 PMG 12 PM10 AMA C A Z Z Z Z F F O O J J J H H H E G 05 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b52"},"rt":8536,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":216382,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"56G 11 AMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b53"},"rt":25239,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":241682,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b54"},"rt":24384,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266130,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b55"},"rt":17064,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":283254,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b56"},"rt":35910,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319226,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b57"},"rt":22482,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341772,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b58"},"rt":5610,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347438,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b59"},"rt":17583,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":365080,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"03 PMZ Z Z X 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b5a"},"rt":26189,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391328,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"07 PM03 PM03 PM12 PM11 AMM O E G G L Z 02 PM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b5b"},"rt":78782,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470166,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMB B O O F G G 10 AM01 PM02 PMX 12 PM12 PMM M M 02 PMX X X B B F F 11 AM11 AMC G G X E G G 11 AM15"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b6c"},"rt":47127,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117574,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,D","hovered":"11 AMA A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b6d"},"rt":19436,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137203,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b6e"},"rt":21981,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159293,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b6f"},"rt":109559,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":268972,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"12 PM12 PM11 AMA A Z Z 12 PM12 PMF F F H H H H 01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b70"},"rt":89519,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":359180,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AMA I 03 PM11 AMH A 10 AMF A A 10 AM11 AMZ C C 09 AM09 AM10 AMO 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b72"},"rt":13560,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":377296,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b73"},"rt":23827,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":401343,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"11 AMO O X M 09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b74"},"rt":47727,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449219,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"01 PMX X X G C F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b75"},"rt":37925,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":487257,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"11 AMB B J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b76"},"rt":47626,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535064,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PMF B B M F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b77"},"rt":12205,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":547570,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b78"},"rt":8059,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":555980,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b79"},"rt":31766,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":587862,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PMZ F 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b7a"},"rt":31366,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":619344,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"I F X X X 11 AMM M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d839e50a7aae4618c88b7b"},"rt":64734,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":684259,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PMX C C F G P G 09 AM"}]
